So this is JIRA's create issue dialog box
这是 JIRA 的创建问题对话框
and the word Issue they're using just
这里使用的单词 issue
like we've been using the word Ticket, just so you know.
意思和罚款单 (ticket) 一样
And as you can see in Issue has an associated Project,
在 issue 中 有一个关联的 Project
an Issue Type, in this case,
还有 Issue Type 在本例中
we're going to call it a bug, and a Summary.
我们选择 Bug 接下来是Summary
In this case, literally everything is broken maybe.
在本例中 我们输入” Literally everything is broken … maybe?”
So, this is a pretty bad bug.
这可是很严重的故障
I'm going to ignore some of these fields here.
下面有些地方可以忽略
But, I'm going to give it a priority of highest and let's have some labels to it.
接下来 我把 Priority 设为 Highest 然后设置一些标签
Maybe you think the issue in the Python code,
或许你认为问题出在 Python 代码中
so I'll type p_y_t and I
因此 我输入pyt
can see up here that an autocomplete is suggesting Python as a label so,
这里可以看到一个自动完成提示 告诉我们可以把Python 作为标签
I can click that, and maybe also I want to give it the label of bug, also a suggestion.
我可以点击这里 然后 我还想添加一个 bug 标签 提示中也有
Now, let's see what happens if I'm not thinking and I tried to add Python again.
现在 让我们看看如果我一时发昏 再次添加 Python 会发生什么
No matches.
没有匹配
Somehow, JIRA is ensuring that this data structure,
JIRA 似乎在确保这个数据结构
not have duplicates of the same label.
不会存在重复的相同标签
Now, there's a data structure in Python that does exactly this,
Python 中有一个数据结构功能完全一样
called the Set and that's what I want to teach you about next.
叫做 Set 后面我们会学习这个数据结构
But, before we do that, let's create our Issue,
但是 首先我们先创建 Issue
and let's click on this Python label.
我们点击这个 Python 标签
And as you can see, this is something that JIRA supports.
你可以看到 这是 JIRA 的一个特色功能
It's showing me everything, with a label of Python,
它可以展示所有带Python 的标签的内容
and it showing me every Issue that has that associated label.
包括每一个带有这个相关标签的 Issue
In the next notebook, you're going to implement
在下一个笔记本中 你将实现
similar functionality to the ticket tracker we've been working with,
与我们之前讨论过的罚款单跟踪器类似的功能
and in doing so, you're going to learn about a new Python data type called
在这个过程中 你会学到一个叫做集合 (set) 的新的Python 数据类型